export const freAndQue = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "How can I avail this special offer?",
    answer:
      "You can make your bookings directly online to avail of the special offer Click Here Alternatively, you can also write to corporate.reservations@ihcltata.com or call on +91 22 60041000 for SeleQtions and Vivanta hotels and reservations@gingerhotels.com or call on 1860-266-3333 for Ginger hotels. Please include/mention your membership number to avail of this offer.",
    isOpen: false,
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "How many times can I avail this special offer?",
    answer:
      "There is no restriction on the number of times you make a booking. Book as many times as possible. However, rooms are subject to availability at the time of booking and there is limited inventory allocated under this offer at individual hotels.",
    isOpen: false,
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question:
      "How many rooms can I book at one time to avail this special offer?",
    answer:
      "You can book up to 3 rooms. Kindly note that you need to be staying at the hotel for the special rates to be applicable.",
    isOpen: false,
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "Can I book the rooms on behalf of my family?",
    answer:
      "You can book a maximum of 3 rooms for yourself and your family per hotel. You are required to accompany your family as a part of this booking. Rooms are subject to availability at the time of booking.",
    isOpen: false,
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question:
      "I am a NeuPass member. Can I earn/redeem my points while availing of this offer?",
    answer:
      "No, this offer is valid for SeleQtions, Vivanta & Ginger hotels in India only.",
    isOpen: false,
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "Can I book hotels in international destinations too?",
    answer:
      "No, this offer is valid at hotels in India only. Valid across SeleQtions, Vivanta and Ginger hotels only",
    isOpen: false,
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "How can I avail of the INR 500 gift voucher?",
    answer:
      "ou will need to share the Gift voucher along with the voucher code and voucher pin at the time of check out/bill settlement to avail of the INR 500 discount, applicable only at Vivanta and SeleQtions hotels only",
    isOpen: false,
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "Can I use this gift voucher every time I make a booking?",
    answer:
      "Kindly note that this is a one-time gift voucher and can be availed only one time. Once utilized the voucher will no longer be valid.",
    isOpen: false,
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question:
      "Who can I contact in case of any issues or clarifications with relation to the program or bookings?",
    answer:
      "You can make your bookings directly online to avail of the special offer Click Here Alternatively, you can also write to corporate.reservations@ihcltata.com or call on +91 22 60041000 for SeleQtions and Vivanta hotels and reservations@gingerhotels.com or call on 1860-266-3333 for Ginger hotels. Please include/mention your membership number to avail of this offer.",
    isOpen: false,
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    question: "How can I avail this special offer?",
    answer:
      "For booking related clarification please write to corporate.reservations@ihcltata.com Or call us on +91 22 60001000 for Vivanta and SeleQtions hotels and reservations@gingerhotels.com or call on 1860-266-3333 for Ginger hotels. For membership related clarification please write to businessconnect@ihcltata.com",
    isOpen: false,
  },
];
